Mss.Ms.Coll.30
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Lecture and Research Notes, 8 linear ft.
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Jules Henry
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Mel J. Herskovits
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--John H. Holmes
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Zora N. Hurston
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Indians
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Jewish holocaust
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--William Jones
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Edward A. Kennard
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--William H. Kilpatrick
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Otto Klineberg
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Alexander Lesser
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Ralph Linton
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Robert H. Lowie
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--May Mandelbaum
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--W. J. McGee
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Margaret Mead
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--William H. Mechling
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Carl Meinhof
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Margaret Mitchell
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--National Research Council
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--William F. Ogburn
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Robert Ogden
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--George Foster Peabody
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Eleanor Phelps
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Archie Phinney
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Race relations
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Race statement
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Paul Radin
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Gladys Reichard
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Joseph Adjei Schandorf
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Erich F. Schmidt
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Thorgues Sie
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Leslie A. Spier
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--H. H. St. Clair
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Wilbur K. Thomas
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Translated correspondence, #1
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Translated correspondence, #2
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Walcott affair
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #1
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #2
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #3
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #4
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #5
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--Booker T. Washington, #6
  - Research notes--Franz Boas--C. G. Woodson
  - Research notes--Carnegie Institute
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport, #1
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport, #2
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Robert Bennett Bean
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Alexander G. Bell
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Franz Boas
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--William E. Castle
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Committee on the American Negro
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Darwin memorial celebration
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--H. H. Donaldson
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Eugenics Committee
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Maurice Fishberg
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Irving Fisher
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Galton Society
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--E. H. Harrisman, Mrs.
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Melville Herskovits
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--F. W. Hooper
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Ales Hrdlicka
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--David S. Jordan
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Madison Grant
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Sidney Gulick
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Lectures
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--John C. Merriam
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--National Research Council--Committee on the Negro
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Henry F. Osborn
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--Paul B. Popenoe
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--T. Wingate Todd
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--William H. Welch
  - Research notes--Charles Davenport--R. S. Woodward
  - Research notes--Henry Herbert Donaldson
  - Research notes--Indians
  - Research notes--H. S. Jennings--Franz Boas
  - Research notes--Louis E. King
  - Research notes--Kenneth M. Ludmerer
  - Research notes--Manuscript collections
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Franz Boas
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Henry H. Donaldson
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Lawrence Foster
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--William K. Gregory
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Melville J. Herskovits
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Bruno Oetteking
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Edward Sapir
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--H. L. Shapiro
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Leslie Spier
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Sara Stevenson
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Leslie A. White
  - Research notes--John Alden Mason--Clark Wissler
  - Research notes--Kelly Miller
  - Research notes--Henry Allen Moe
  - Research notes--National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - Research notes--Robert C. Ogden
  - Research notes--Elsie Clews Parsons
  - Research notes--Race relations
  - Research notes--Reprints--Joseph B. Aceves
  - Research notes--Reprints--African-American Education
  - Research notes--Reprints--African-American Explorers
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lee G. Alexander
  - Research notes--Reprints--Anthropology
  - Research notes--Reprints--Herbert Aptheker
  - Research notes--Reprints--Harold Baron
  - Research notes--Reprints--Fredrik Barth
  - Research notes--Reprints--Warren Beckwith
  - Research notes--Reprints--John W. Blassingame
  - Research notes--Reprints--Donald Bonder
  - Research notes--Reprints--Elizabeth Brandt
  - Research notes--Reprints--Daniel G. Brinton
  - Research notes--Reprints--Erness B. Brody
  - Research notes--Reprints--Nathan Brody
  - Research notes--Reprints--David I. Bushnell, Jr.
  - Research notes--Reprints--Donald J. Calista
  - Research notes--Reprints--Robert L. Carneiro
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alexander F. Chamberlain
  - Research notes--Reprints--K. C. Chang
  - Research notes--Reprints--Simeon W. Chilungu
  - Research notes--Reprints--Charles H. Coe
  - Research notes--Reprints--M. M. Cohen
  - Research notes--Reprints--Juan Comas
  - Research notes--Reprints--James W. Covington, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--James W. Covington, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--William Cunningham
  - Research notes--Reprints--Philip D. Curtin
  - Research notes--Reprints--Regna Darnell
  - Research notes--Reprints--Charles Benedict Davenport
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ralph W. Dexter
  - Research notes--Reprints--G. S. Dickerman
  - Research notes--Reprints--J. L. Dillard
  - Research notes--Reprints--W. E. B. DuBois
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alan Dundes
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alfreda M. Duster
  - Research notes--Reprints--Robert Ernst
  - Research notes--Reprints--Charles H. Fairbanks
  - Research notes--Reprints--William H. Ferris
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lewis S. Feuer
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ann Fischer
  - Research notes--Reprints--Regina Flannery
  - Research notes--Reprints--Daryll Forde
  - Research notes--Reprints--E. Franklin Frazier
  - Research notes--Reprints--John F. Freeman
  - Research notes--Reprints--Morton H. Fried, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Morton H. Fried, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--Max Friedemann
  - Research notes--Reprints--Edward I. Fry
  - Research notes--Reprints--James P. Gallagher
  - Research notes--Reprints--Nathan Glazer
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ricardo Godoy
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alexander A. Goldenweiser
  - Research notes--Reprints--James B. Griffin
  - Research notes--Reprints--G. Stanley Hall
  - Research notes--Reprints--A. Irving Hallowell
  - Research notes--Reprints--E. A. Hammond
  - Research notes--Reprints--Marvin Harris
  - Research notes--Reprints--R. K. Harris
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ira E. Harrison
  - Research notes--Reprints--Michael J. Harner
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lilla Mills Hawes
  - Research notes--Reprints--Robert Heine-Geldern
  - Research notes--Reprints--Melville J. Herskovits, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Melville J. Herskovits, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--J. N. B. Hewitt
  - Research notes--Reprints--George L. Hicks
  - Research notes--Reprints--S. J. Holmes
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ales Hrdlicka
  - Research notes--Reprints--Langston Hughes
  - Research notes--Reprints--Harriet Pinckney Huse
  - Research notes--Reprints--Dell Hymes
  - Research notes--Reprints--International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
  - Research notes--Reprints--Jewish Race and Religion
  - Research notes--Reprints--David Kaplan
  - Research notes--Reprints--H. Gill King
  - Research notes--Reprints--L. King
  - Research notes--Reprints--Christopher Lasch
  - Research notes--Reprints--Edmund R. Leach
  - Research notes--Reprints--William L. Leap
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alfred Leipzig
  - Research notes--Reprints--Irving A. Leonard
  - Research notes--Reprints--Williston H. Lofton
  - Research notes--Reprints--Rayford W. Logan
  - Research notes--Reprints--Cherry Lowman-Vayda
  - Research notes--Reprints--Barbara and Thomas Lynch
  - Research notes--Reprints--Jacques J. Maquet
  - Research notes--Reprints--Luis Martin
  - Research notes--Reprints--William A. Massey
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lyle N. McAlister
  - Research notes--Reprints--August Meier
  - Research notes--Reprints--Sidney W. Mintz, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Sidney W. Mintz, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--Jedediah Morse
  - Research notes--Reprints--Richard K. Murdoch, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Richard K. Murdoch, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--Ferdinand E. Okada
  - Research notes--Reprints--George S. Painter
  - Research notes--Reprints--John H. Peterson, Jr.
  - Research notes--Reprints--Woodbine Potter
  - Research notes--Reprints--Race, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Race, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--Race, #3
  - Research notes--Reprints--Bob Scholte
  - Research notes--Reprints--William Haynes Simmons
  - Research notes--Reprints--Elliot P. Skinner
  - Research notes--Reprints--Daniel M. Smith
  - Research notes--Reprints--Harlan I. Smith
  - Research notes--Reprints--Bernhard J. Stern
  - Research notes--Reprints--Julian H. Steward
  - Research notes--Reprints--George W. Stocking
  - Research notes--Reprints--Norman W. Storer
  - Research notes--Reprints--Dee Ann Story
  - Research notes--Reprints--William C. Sturtevant, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--William C. Sturtevant, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--William C. Sturtevant, #3
  - Research notes--Reprints--Merze Tate
  - Research notes--Reprints--Charlton W. Tebeau
  - Research notes--Reprints--Elisabeth Tooker
  - Research notes--Reprints--George L. Trager
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lothar L. Tresp
  - Research notes--Reprints--Unknown Authors
  - Research notes--Reprints--Charles A. Valentine
  - Research notes--Reprints--Fred W. Voget
  - Research notes--Reprints--Alexander Walters
  - Research notes--Reprints--Booker T. Washington, #1
  - Research notes--Reprints--Booker T. Washington, #2
  - Research notes--Reprints--Waldo R. Wedel
  - Research notes--Reprints--Fred Wendorf
  - Research notes--Reprints--Lucy L. Wenhold
  - Research notes--Reprints--Leslie A. White
  - Research notes--Reprints--William Appleman Williams
  - Research notes--Reprints--Carter G. Woodson
  - Research notes--Reprints--Louise Wore
  - Research notes--Reprints--Monroe N. Work
  - Research notes--Reprints--Peter Worsley
  - Research notes--Carl Schurz
  - Research notes--Survey of Native American Languages
  - Research notes--Leon Fradley Whitney
  - Research notes--Carter G. Woodson
- Series III. Works, 1 linear ft.
  - Black Anthropologists
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #1
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #2
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #3
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #4
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #5
  - Blacks and the Southern Indians, #6
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #1
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #2
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #3
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #4
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #5
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #6
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #7
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #8
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #9
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #10
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #11
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #12
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #13
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #14
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #15
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #16
  - Boas goes to Atlanta, #17
  - Franz Boas and the Origin of Afro-American Studies
  - Franz Boas and the Study of Black Folklore
  - Franz Boas, Black students, and the study of Black problems
  - Cherokee in the Trade...Southeast, 1670-1800, Charts
  - Colonial Conflict and the Cherokee Indians, 1710-1760, Bound volume
  - Divide and Rule: Red, White, and Black in the Southeast, 1963
  - Friends and Brothers
  - Fusion and Separation, #1
  - Fusion and Separation, #2
  - Fusion and Separation, #3
  - Fusion and Separation, #4
  - History of the Second Seminole War, 1970
    General note
    Review
    Mahon,, J.K.
  - The Hopi Way
  - The Neglected Achievement of Alexander McGillivray
  - The Nation of Bread, 1957
  - Patrilineal Institutions in Southeastern North America, 1963
  - Priests and War Chiefs, #1
  - Priests and War Chiefs, #2
  - Priests and War Chiefs, #3
  - Priests and War Chiefs, #4
  - Priests and War Chiefs, #5
  - Red-Black Mixture
  - Skeletons in the Anthropological Closet (Abstract)
  - Southeastern Political Units in the Eighteenth Century
  - The Trading Gun of the Southern Indians
- Series IV. Photographs and Ephemera, 0.5 linear ft.
  - William S. Willis, Howard University yearbook, photograph, 1942; 1.0 Photograph(s); Bust length portrait of Willis during student years.
  - Scrapbook, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Willis, walking down steps, pipe in hand.
    - William S. Willis on the steps of the American Philosophical Society
    - William S. Willis, teaching class.
  - Newspaper clippings
  - Certificate--Howard University, 1942
  - Certificate--American Association for Advancement of Science, 1962
  - Certificate--Armed Forces Recognition, 1984
  - Photograph--Franz Boas
  - Photograph--Painting by Indians
  - Photograph--William S. Willis, Jr., 1955
  - Photographs--William S. Willis, 1979
  - Photographic negative--Certificate--Ph.D. Columbia University, 1955